State Penitentiary for the Eastern District of Pennsylvania Records 1819-1892 Mss.365.P381p
American Philosophical Society
- Series IV. Prisoners' Correspondence, 1845-1955; 2 folders
  - Correspondence about the prisoners' letters, 1953-1955; 10 items
    - To Raymond Larcombe, 1953 Nov. 11; TLS Cy, 1p.; Gruber, Jacob W. (Folder 2)
    - To Jacob W. Gruber, 1953 Nov. 14; TLS, 1p.; Marin, Norman H. (Folder 2)
    - To Edward C. Starr, 1953 Nov. 17; TLS Cy, 1p.; Gruber, Jacob W. (Folder 2)
    - To Jacob W. Gruber, 1953 Nov. 19; TLS, 2p.; Starr, Edward C. (Folder 2)
    - To Edward C. Starr, 1953 Nov. 20; TLS Cy, 1p.; Gruber, Jacob W. (Folder 2)
    - To Jacob W. Gruber, 1953 Nov. 23; TLS, 1p.; Starr, Edward C. (Folder 2)
    - To Jacob W. Gruber, 1955 Jan. 6; ALS, 1p.; Larcombe, Ray (Folder 2)
    - To Rose Larcombe, 1955 Feb. 28; TLS Cy, 1p.; Gruber, Jacob W. (Folder 2)
    - To Jacob W. Gruber, 1955 Mar. 5; ALS, 1p.; Larcombe, Rose (Folder 2)
    - "Jews in the Eastern State Penitentiary in the 19th century", n.d.; TMsS, 6p.; Gruber, Jacob W. (Folder 2)